const quizHelpingVerbs = [
    {
      question: "Manakah dari berikut ini yang merupakan helping verb?",
      options: ["eat", "sleep", "is", "play"],
      answer: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "Kalimat mana yang menggunakan helping verb dengan benar?",
      options: [
        "She running fast.",
        "She is running fast.",
        "She run fast.",
        "She running is fast.",
      ],
      answer: 1,
    },
    {
      question: 'Pilih kalimat yang menggunakan “has” sebagai helping verb:',
      options: [
        "She has a dog.",
        "She has been working hard.",
        "She has fast.",
        "She has run fast yesterday.",
      ],
      answer: 1,
    },
    {
      question: 'Kalimat mana yang menggunakan “was” sebagai helping verb?',
      options: [
        "He was sleeping when I arrived.",
        "He was tired.",
        "He was happy.",
        "He was teacher.",
      ],
      answer: 0,
    },
    {
      question:
        '“Can” termasuk jenis kata apa dalam kalimat ini? → “She can swim well.”',
      options: ["Main verb", "Helping verb", "Adjective", "Noun"],
      answer: 1,
    },
    {
      question:
        "Manakah yang merupakan pasangan kata kerja utama dan bantu yang benar?",
      options: ["is eating", "go walk", "eat jump", "plays runs"],
      answer: 0,
    },
    {
      question:
        "Kalimat mana yang menunjukkan bentuk future tense dengan helping verb?",
      options: [
        "She eat tomorrow.",
        "She will eat tomorrow.",
        "She eats tomorrow.",
        "She eating tomorrow.",
      ],
      answer: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "Kalimat mana yang mengandung dua helping verbs?",
      options: [
        "I am working.",
        "I have worked.",
        "I have been studying.",
        "I study well.",
      ],
      answer: 2,
    },
    {
      question: 'Kalimat mana yang menggunakan “do” sebagai helping verb?',
      options: [
        "I do my homework.",
        "Do you like pizza?",
        "I do tired.",
        "I do a good student.",
      ],
      answer: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "Kalimat mana yang tidak mengandung helping verb?",
      options: [
        "She is going.",
        "They have played.",
        "He was sleeping.",
        "He runs fast.",
      ],
      answer: 3,
    },
  ];
  
  export default quizHelpingVerbs;
  